Every social species depends on communication.
Humans are no exception.
So why can't we communicate with our devices?
With Macbook Voice, now you can.
Macbook, on.
Macbook Voice: Good morning, Daven. What would
you like to do today?
Macbook, open up a new browser window.
Okay, opening
new browser window.
(success music)
[Narrator]: Experience the most natural user interface
ever created.
Mouse up.
[Macbook]: Mouse has moved up.
Click.
[Macbook]: Would you like to left click, or right click?
You know what?
I'd like to left click.
[Macbook]: Okay.
[Macbook CHIMES]
[Narrator]: Keep your documents safe.
[Macbook]: This
command requires your password.
Uh, "big boy".
[Macbook]: I didn't get that. Please speak
your password.
Big boy.
[Macbook]: I didn't get that. Please speak your password.
BIG.
BOY.
[Macbook]: I didn't get tha-
[Narrator]: Designed to fit your lifestyle,
the Macbook Voice will make you more productive than ever before.
I think I did pretty good.
Hey, we should
go for coffee this weekend.
Hey, we should go for coffee this weekend.
[Macbook]: Okay,
[Macbook]: looking for coffee shops in your area.
But you're not buying this time.
[Macbook]: Buying coffee shops
in your area
You know, I've got to give you credit.
[Macbook]: Transferring credit card information
to coffee shops in Canada.
[Narrator]: Macbook Voice. We should talk.
[SONG: "PANDA" BY: "DESIIGNER"]
Closed Captioning by: Kate Colenbrander